Guide to the Lee Felsenstein Papers M1443
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2: Golemics
  - Subseries 2.8: Business Records
    - Hackers, The Movie: proposal, book drafts, correspondence, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Lee Felsenstein's Talk at Pitzer College Reconstructing the Agora, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Sequitur materials, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Sequitur for non-profits, inventory, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - The Bridgebuilders Project, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - 103-Mechanical schematics, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Public Terminal Adapter-schematics, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Job 128 - Schedule and Budget (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Job 122, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Osiris, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Job 119, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Job 123, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Job 124 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Job 125, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Job 129, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Job 136, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - ParcPlace (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - VCR (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - VCR/IR/Link (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - LF-Biographical/CV (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Proposals, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - CB, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Geissberger, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - McNally (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Micro-Illusions (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - OKI ROM Sale/Lic (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - RICOH CCA, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Mentor Sale, 1984-1986 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Rental Agreement-2398 4th, 1984-1986 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Computer Museum, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Patent-Sol, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - FCC Code, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Golemics Prospects, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Auction of Furniture, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Ronin List to Enter, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 46)
    - Ronin, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 47)
    - 16-bit UNIX Systems Slides (Box 23, Folder 48)
    - Articles in Progress, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 49)
    - 2.3.2 Fabrication, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - 6.5.6 Survivor's Club, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 51)
    - Resumes (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - Hacker info, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 53)
    - HACK-TIC, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 55)
    - Hacker's Conference, 1987-1991 (Box 23, Folder 56)
    - Asilomar, 1986-1991 (Box 23, Folder 58)
    - ACM, 1984-1985 (Box 23, Folder 59)
    - Sprint 8.6.1, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 61)
    - Phone, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Paid and Unpaid bills, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Employment Development Department (EDD), 1988 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Invoices, 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - The Practice of Creativity by George M. Prince: paperback book, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - New Think by Edward de Bono: paperback book, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - The Universal Traveler by Don Koberg and Jim Bagnall: paperback book, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - U.S. Small Business Administration-management aids, 1980-1984 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Book chapter, The Tyranny of Structurelessness by Joreen, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Consumer Cooperatives-newsletters and info (David Chilcott), 1981 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Consumer Cooperatives-newsletters and info (David Chilcott), 1978 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Newsletters: The Circular-Consumer Information Report (by Bank of America), 1982 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Ricoh Fax Machine-info, correspondence, sales agreement, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Golemics deposits, 1988-1989 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Cooperative (Co-op) Bank Info, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Bank Statements, 1988-1989 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Income, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Golemics-bank reconciliations, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Revenue, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Ledger, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Institute for Preventative Medicine (IPM) health plan, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - American Qualified Plans, Inc. ESOP Consultants, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Bylaws of Project Artaud Corp, Stock Restriction Agreement, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Building Social Change Communities by the Training Action Affinity Group and A Primer for Community Research by Clifford V. Levy, 1972 - 1976 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Workers Trust-services for the Democratic Workplace, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Industrial Cooperative Association, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1988-1992 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Lee Felsenstein's Talks re: Personal Computer Development, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Lee Felsenstein's address change (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous schematics, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Siliscape, RED, Ukranian Institute of Radio Technology, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Golemics, paid bills, Jan. - June 1984 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Fantasy/Prestige/Milestone/Stax phone service-paid bills, 1983 - 1984 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Contract Services, paid bills, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Golemics-paid bills, A-K, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Golemics-paid bills, L-M, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Golemics-paid bills, N-Q, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Golemics-paid bills, R-Z, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Golemics-paid expense reports, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Golemics-old draft of business plan, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Golemics-paid bills, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Paid Expense Reports, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Schwabacher-Frey invoices, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Golemics-paid bills, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Golemics-paid bills, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Paid Bills: AFCO, AT&T, BancAmerica, Hamilton/Avnet, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Paid Bills: Pacific Bell, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Paid Bills: Mentor Graphics, Multi-Protection Trust, Plexus, Western Union, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Expense Reports: Lee Felsenstein, J. Bourgein, Elaina Malm, Jeff Milstead, Mimi Montgomery, misc., 1985 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Paid Bills: contract services, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Bank Statements, Deposits, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Bank Statements, Deposits, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Bank Statements, Deposits, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Bank Statements, Deposits, 1979-1981 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Golemics-paid bills, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Dun and Bradstreet report for Chief Executive of Golemics, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Packing Slips, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Lee Felsenstein's Ronin Manifesto, 03-26-1987 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Staff Personal Information: Adams, Athanasiou, Behling, Bonthron, Bullis, Chapman, Coaster, Cook, Conrad, Dickie, Fosse, Hamilton, Heinstein, Helton, Ingraham, Jacobs, Karpinski, Keachie, Kelsey, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Staff Personal Information: Miles, Montgomery, Reykjalin, Paulsell, Stauduhar, Thomas, Webster, Weisse, Williams, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Software status and schedules, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - National Accounts, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - A/C Information, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Accounts File Maintenance-Master File, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Product File Maintenance-Master File, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Vendor File Maintenance-Master File, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Purchase Orders File Maintenance-Master File, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Golemics-products, Seybold seminars, Aldus Corp., Manhattan Graphics, Union for Democratic Communications, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Strategies Foundation, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Museums using Golemics' products, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Colby Research Industries-DBA Colby Computer Beta Test, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Electronic Cafe 1984 Olympics in Los Angeles (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - #102-Microsoft MACRO Assembler, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - #102-Microsoft GW Basic information, extensions, correspondence, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Golemics CD ROM Resident BIOS, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - #102-Roger Chapman, Microsoft GW Basic, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - #102-specifications, Microsoft GW Basic, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Microsoft Graphics BASIC 2.0-Configuration Questionnaire, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Golemics cancelled checks, 1979-1983 (Box 26, Folder 25-26)
    - Payment Schedules, Earnings Reports, Ledgers, 1983-1986 (Box 26, Folder 27-28)
    - Wlonk Soft, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Viewgraphs-presentation on history of microcomputing, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - AST TurboLaser description; Z-Soft Newsletter, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Image Input, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - ANSI time and control code for video/audio, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Mentor Graphics, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Data I/O Corporation, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Rede Corporation, Stone House Conference notes, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - Golemics personnel / company information, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - PinList Proto 1, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - Color Print, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - Product offers, copyright information, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 43)
    - Quintar bugs, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 44)
    - Character fonts, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 45)
    - Upstart Corp., status of technology, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 46)
    - Immediate Correspondence, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 47)
    - Golemics letterhead stationary (Box 28, Folder 48)
    - Design Review, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 49)
    - Program by Robert Bickford to operate a Token-Ring LAN adapter card, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Token-Ring LAN Adapter materials, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Job 112 work outline, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Starter Kit-SCSI BUS Interface Controller, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Company information-Versatec (Xerox) and FutureNet (Data I/O), 1987 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Board Fabrication and Assembly, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Company information-Mr. Wizzard's PC Shop, Aerosceintific, DVK, UTC, Solectron, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Articles of Interest, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - ROM BIOS backup record, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Job 112-plans and schematics, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Spirit by Lee Felsenstein, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Mathematical problems, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Lee Felsenstein-resume, cover letter, expense report, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Golemics-paid bills, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Golemics-financial information, 1982-1985 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Preliminary Budget-info for estimations, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Golemics business records, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Payment Detail-Contractors, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Lillian Lea, E.A., 1984 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Golemics letterhead stationary (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Colorblind peripherals, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Pacific Software, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Pacific Mutual insurance, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Finances, Credit Cards, 1979-1981 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Old checks and deposit slips, 1979-1984 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Closed purchase orders, 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Closed purchase orders (vendors: A-H), 1984 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Closed purchase orders (vendors: I-O), 1984 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Closed purchase orders (vendors: P-Z), 1984 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - S. Clay Wilson comic book; party photos, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 16)
      Contains photographs
    - Management Theory, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Employee Relations, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Computer Industry-related media coverage, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Computer Faire, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - CPU Board, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - RAM Board, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - DMA Board, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Keyboard / Speaker Board, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - FDC Board, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Job 109 Video - A, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Video RAM Board Video_B, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Video Output Video_C, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Parallel / Serial Board, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Job 109-SCSI, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Job 109-video, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Job 109-schedule; Alpha DC, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Job 109-KBD, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - System Phone, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Job 111-contract, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Crowntek and Waterloo Port Info, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - SBC-16, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - B-L IPI/IDM Proposal, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - IPI-3 > IDM-500, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - "Polyfidelity: Sex in the Kerista Commune..."; other Kerista documents, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      Contains a paperback book
    - MacroEconomic Art Project, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - The Node newsletter, volume 1 issue 1, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Small Business seminar, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - EMM Spec 3.20, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Tedrick-Higbee Insurance Service, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Cable Co-op (Palo Alto), 1985 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - William T. Price, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Terminal Committee, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous schematics, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - The I/O-11, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Paperless Accounting, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - SCSI / PLUS, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Sunwind, Ltd. electric car, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Patent information, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Requests for ROM chip that emulates IBM PCs, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Hacker's Mac: inquiries, newsletters, etc., 1985 (Box 31, Folder 23-24)
    - Apollo Stuff, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Apollo Domain Users Society (ADUS) and Mentor User's Group (MUG), 1987 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Sequitur information, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Notes on pixel administration (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Storage shed in Berkeley-lease, correspondence, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - VME Video Display Generator, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Expander Sales, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - LF / JB weekly meetings, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Coin Box-Dick Grey, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Key Specifications, Object Code, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - Aaron's Pascal Code, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - Reddy Information System, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - WISCO, Knowledge Industries, Lee Felsenstein, The Development Process, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - SCSI and miscellaneous Programs, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Schematics, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - IBM AIXpert Journal-first issue, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Photos and negatives (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - The Washington Technology Center, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Vendor publications and newsletters, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - KPFA radio station, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Sequitur-buyout possibles, inquiries, info requests, software reviewers, other misc., 1985 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Resumes, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Compatibility of hardware / software, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Lee Felsenstein's correspondence with: OKI Telecom, Samsung, Microsoft, E. Mazer, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - GESI / DIAQUEST, Sony Authoring, A Squared Systems, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Job 128 (Liz Rich and Co.) - schematics and correspondence, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Job 105-Ricoh, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - PC-Fax, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Britton-Lee The Communicating Database (CDB), 1985 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Multibus-UNIX Board Sets, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Cables and chips, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Analog Board, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Audio Synthesis, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Schematic Markups, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Reddy Information Systems, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous projects' correspondence, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Liz Rich and Co. correspondence, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Program designed by Ned Lagin, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Purchase Orders, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Purchase Orders, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Purchase Orders, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Capital Equipment Inventory, 1983-1987 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Parts Inventory, 1983-1987 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Payroll Ledgers and Data, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Bob Marsh, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Paid Bills, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Job 116-correspondence, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Vendor quotations, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Financial Guarantees made by Golemics, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Promissory Notes-payable, receivable, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Lee Felsenstein personal: finances, loans, real estate, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Insurance Coverage, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Income Tax Returns, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Paid Bills-Copy Mat, Photo Tech, DHL, Fed Ex, B of A, HCL, Kaiser, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Paid Bills-LGC Engineering, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Stock Options, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Paid Bills-UPS, US Courier, Saul Zaentz, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Paid Bills, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 20-21)
    - Expense Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Paid Consultants, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous materials of interest, varied dates, 1980-1990 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Golemics Archives [old register] (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - 40 count-5-1/4 Floppy Disks [8]: various (Box 34, Folder 1-8)
    - Installation Manuals, User Guides, 1987-1989 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Software-2 reels film tape (Upstart) (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Software-2 reels film tape (various) (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - 2 count-software programs on paper tape rolls (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 2.9: Schematics
    - Drawings and schematics, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Rainbow Video Board, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Schematics, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Job 116 binder, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      includes schematics and miscellaneous project plans
    - Job 116 binder 'MC', 1987 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Job 116 binder LF, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Job 116 binder Host I/F, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Job 116 binder DC Display Controller, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Job 116 binder Image Processor, Video Output, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Job 116 binder, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Job 116 binder I/O Expansion, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Job 116 binder Jeff's Notes, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Job 116 binder, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Job 116 binder, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Job 116 binder, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Job 116 binder WAR, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Job 116 binder, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Job 116 binder, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Job 116 binder, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Notebook labeled LGC Engineering from folder labeled Vector Specific (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - The Finger, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - IBM Proto Card, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Video Patents, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Job 116 schematics, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Job 109 (Fax-PC prototype) plans and schematics, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - DMA schematics, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Job 110 (Scanner I/F for Ricoh) plans and schematics, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - Thermal-main PC, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - Bob Flexer-history, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - Mouse specs, other schematics, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 50)
    - Job 113-PC SCSI I/F specs (Rancho Technology), 1986 (Box 28, Folder 51)
    - Job 117-OKI Electric Industry, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 52)
    - Job 114-plans and schematics, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 53)
    - Job 102-plans and schematics, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 54)
    - Job 115-plans and schematics (Colorblind), 1986 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Job 113-plans and schematics, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Job 109-plans and schematics, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Job 110-plans and schematics (Ricoh scanner), 1986 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Job 111-SCI LISTS, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Britton-Lee PC Specs, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Job 116-plans and schematics, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Various business cards, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Information on PC Expansion Board Brackets, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - 1.1.3 Interrupt 8259, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous schematics and component layouts, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Effect of LAN Buffer Size on System Performance; Coinbox Timer, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Job 116-old component layouts, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Design drawings and component layouts (Flat-box 36)
    - Design drawings and component layouts (Flat-box 37)
    - Design drawings and component layouts (Flat-box 38)
    - Design drawings and component layouts (Flat-box 39)
    - Design drawings and component layouts (Flat-box 40)
    - Design drawings and component layouts (Flat-box 41)
    - Oversized folder of design drawings and component layouts (Map-folder 1)
- Series 3: Homebrew Computer Club
  - Lee Felsenstein: proposing An Online Homebrew Computer Club, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Homebrew T-Shirt Orders, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Series 4: LGC Engineering
  - Subseries 4.1: Correspondence
    - LGC correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - LGC miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Early LGC-Squawk Box, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Early LGC-[correspondence], 1975 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Early LGC-[computer club correspondence, newsletters], 1975 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Early LGC-[correspondence], 1975 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Embosser that marks, Loving Grace Cybernetics-Incorporated, 03-21-1977 (Box 9, Folder 33)
      stainless steel embosser
    - Apple Computer, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Subseries 4.2: Publications
    - Early LGC-A Real Time All Digital Musical Synthesizer, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Early LGC-Preliminary Design for a Run-Length Decoding Video Generator (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Early LGC-Computer Club Newsletters, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Early LGC-Computer Club Conventions, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Homebrew Computer Club, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Journal of Community Communications, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 18)
      This is the pre first issue; it includes article about Community Memory Project by Ken Colstad and Efram Lipkin of LGC. Also contains information about the Tom Swift Terminal: Convivial Cybernetic Device.
    - Early LGC-[computer club newsletters], 1975 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Early LGC-[computer club correspondence, newsletters], 1975 (Box 9, Folder 21-24)
  - Subseries 4.3: Promotional Materials
    - Early LGC-Diablo manuals, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Early LGC-Martin Spergel, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 4.4: Business Records
    - Agreements (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - LGC blanks forms, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - LGC rent and utilities, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - LGC accounts payable, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Marketing Materials (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Community Memory Project articles, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - "Rehabilitation Information Project" by David L. Jaffe of the Palo Alto VA Medical Center, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Transfer of title, cost factors, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Three River-Seq, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - LGC documents, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - LGC invoices, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - The Institute of Ecotechnics (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Sequitur materials, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Modem, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Pennywhistle, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - LGC miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - A Building Block Approach to High Quality Graphics by Flexer and Wiederhold (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Monitor (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Sol-22, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Joystick/Flywheel, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Contracts, Invoices, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 22)